

Business Administrator & Interactive Media Designer



+1 (470) 667 6382



danielagonzaless@hotmail.com linkedin.com/in/danielagonzalezsarria

Ottawa, ON, Canada

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Business Administrator and Interactive Media Design student with UX/UI design and web development experience. Excellent creative and analytical skills, with a strong desire to learn new things. Team worker with a keen sense of detail.

EDUCATION

Interactive Media Design Algonquin College



Awards:

- Dean's Honours List I, II, & III semesters (Currently doing IV)
- Cumulative G.P.A 3.97 / 4.0

Bachelor of Business Administration Icesi University

🔾 Cali, Valle, Colombia 📛 January 2016 - February 2021

Thesis title: "Generation Z vs. Higher Education"

Thesis supervisor: Professor Tatiana Cortavarria

Awards:

- Honour roll VII to X semester
- Awarded 1st Place Best Business Plan May 2020
- Awarded 1st Place "Experience at the point of sale" for the company Fiore - Nov 2019
- 1st Place May 2016 Business Competition Award, "Free" topic, "Innovation" category & "Best Oral & Written Support"

PROGRAM-RELATED SKILLS

- Microsoft Office: Excel, Word, PowerPoint, & Outlook
- Adobe: Illustrator, XD, Photoshop, Audition, Premiere Pro, & Lightroom Classic
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, & Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Basecamp, Figma, Miro, Maze, & Asana
- AS-400

SKILLS

- Wireframe creation
- Design Thinking
- Web Design
- Teamwork / Organize
- Orientation to results
- Assertive communication

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- Portuguese (Fluent)

EXPERIENCE

Administrative Assistant Apex Motor Express

🔾 Ottawa, Ontario, Canada 📋 Feb, 2023 - Currently

Experienced Administrative Assistant skilled in logistics, AS-400 manifest management, and exceptional customer service. Expert in appointment scheduling, dispatching, and financial accuracy.

Community Manager & Logistics Amorango

🔾 Ribeirão Preto, São Paulo, Brasil 📛 Jun, 2019 - Nov, 2021

Versatile Professional with a proven ability to manage supplier relationships, drive customer attraction, and marketing efforts. Expert in negotiation, social media management, quality control, and promoting community engagement.

Persona Natural (Natural Person Business) Entrepreneurship, Owner

Results-driven professional with a solid background in catalog clothing sales and extensive experience in nurturing client and supplier relationships. Skilled in problem-solving, financial management, and actively contributing employment growth in Colombia.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Web Development **Projects**

In my projects, I've built responsive websites with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and JavaScript, including a dynamic quiz site with QuizAPI integration. I've also designed and wireframed with Adobe XD, advancing from low to high fidelity, and managed communication, assignments, and coordination through BaseCamp.

UX / UI and Graphic Design **Projects**

Designed a commercial mobile app using Figma and conducted usability tests with Maze. Proficient in Adobe Illustrator for scalable graphics and illustrations, ensuring multi-platform compatibility.

REFERENCES

Apex Motor Express:

Advantage Personnel:

John Boersma - +1 (613) 223 4026 Alexandra Boies - +1 (613) 232 0100 jboersma@apexltl.com

ottawa@onyourteam.com